IGERE OVIE.O

PRODUCT DESIGNER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Contact

Lagos state, Nigeria (708) 026-2206 ovieigere@gmail.com

PROFILE

Quality oriented professional with 2 years of experience and proven knowledge of product design & front-end engineering frameworks and technologies. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the product design role at your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kardinal, Yaba — Product designer

2022 - present

Skills: - Ui/UX | Figma | Material ui | Adobe photoshop | Jira

A business travel platform reimagining how business travel, connect and collaborate with their remote and distributed employees by providing them with one platform that optimizes how their employees travel within cities connect and collaborate with their client.

- Professional execution of the design and implementation of user flows and interactions.
- · Maintain, updating and improving existing designs
- · Implementing layouts and prototyping.
- Supervised front-end developers with design, building user interfaces using React and its libraries.

Prembly, Freelance — *UI designer*

2022 - 2022

Skills:- Ui/UX | Figma | Material ui | Adobe photoshop | Jira | Slack

A business travel platform reimagining how business travel, connect and collaborate with their remote and distributed employees by providing them with one platform that optimizes how their employees travel within cities connect and collaborate with their client.

- Professional execution of the design and implementation of user flows and interactions.
- Designed a mobile/desktop site for a new management Software School during a four-week UI/UX design competition.
- · Conducted user research to identify key features and pain points, created

PROFILE LINKS

Portfolio: oveey.dev

Github: <u>@oveey</u>

LinkedIn: @oveey

Version control

·Git

·Github

Project management

· Slack,

·Jira

Skills

- ·Ui/Ux design
- Figma
- ·Material Ui
- ·Adobe photoshop
- ·HTML5
- ·CSS3
- TAILWIND CSS
- · JAVASCRIPT

wireframes and a prototype, and applied key design principles.

• Conducted multiple rounds of user testing to ensure an intuitive and user-friendly experience. Received positive feedback from both judges and users.

UPWORK, USA — *Graphic designer*

2020 - present

Skills:- Adobe photoshop | Canva | Adobe illustrator

- Collaborating closely with clients in order to conceptualize, design, develop and implement graphic layouts and materials such as logos, flyers, brochures, infographics and adverts.
- Supervised the assessment of all graphic materials in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the design.
- Designing high fidelity quality graphics based on specific requirements.

EDUCATION

University of lagos, Lagos — Computer science **2022**

AlT school africa, Lagos — front-end development 2022